https://cal-ore.com/privacy-policy/

HomeAir ServicesAir Medical TeamsAircraft & EquipmentAir Ambulance BasesAir Ambulance FAQsRequest Air Medical Service InformationGround ServicesGround Medical TeamsGround EquipmentGround Service FAQsRequest Ground Service InformationAbout UsManagement TeamCommunity InvolvementEmployment OpportunitiesCal-Ore CaresContact UsMembershipEnrollmentFAQsTerms & ConditionsMerchant Discount ProgramCAL-ORE Training Institute
Cal-Ore Life Flight Privacy PolicyOur Commitment To Privacy Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used.The Information We Collect This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the Cal-Ore Life Flight website. On some pages, you can order products, make requests and register for classes or to receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages are: name, address, email address, phone number and credit card information.On some pages, you can submit information about other people. For example, if you order a gift online and want it sent directly to the recipient, you will need to submit the recipient’s address. In this circumstance, the types of personal information collected are: name, address, phone number, and possibly email address. We will not use this information for any other purpose other than processing your request.The Way We Use Information Information you provide about yourself when placing an order or requesting information is used only to complete that order or information request. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order.We use the information you provide about someone else when placing an order only to process the order and to confirm delivery. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order.We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties.Information you submit will not be used for any other purpose and is not shared with outside parties except to complete your request. In some cases, such as when you purchase a product from our Cal-Ore store, you will be directed to another website. Please refer to their privacy policy when there. Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.Our Commitment to Data Security To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.Our Commitment to Children’s Privacy Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.How To Contact Us Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please call us at (800) 761-5183 or send us an email at� info@cal-ore.com.
